Okay. So we, we got, we got to, we got to talk about the no Kings protests. We got to do it.
We got to do it. Because first of all, they're not protests, they're rallies. And it's very
important to identify the difference so that we actually know the expected efficacy of our efforts.
Now a rally is meant to rally folks around an idea, a team, okay. And that is a time of kind of like
concerted celebration or concerted information sharing, et cetera. We can call the no Kings a
rally because it's only happening for two hours from 10 to 12. It's also requiring people to
register, which if we talk about protests, particularly in a fascist state where surveillance
is now very loudly and outspoken, what kind of actual protest would essentially incriminate
its participants by having them put their information into a database.
Now I'm not going to say that the whole no Kings thing is completely useless. However, there are
no clear demands being made and there are no clear actions that are being asked for from the people
at the rally. Protest is meant to demonstrate the might of the people to the ruling class,
to the powers that be. The protest is supposed to be basically a unified, it's supposed to make them
shook. So if your protest has a beginning time, it doesn't disrupt anything, baby, that's not
resistance. And it's imperative that we identify what actual resistance is because I don't want people
to continue to be tricked into thinking they're really resisting. You're not, you're actually a
part of controlled opposition, not organized opposition. And the two are not the same because
when it's controlled, the question becomes who's controlling when it's organized, you know who it is
and you know what the goal is. Sister seals, this is your ancestor, Harriet Tubman.